Keep yourself centered.
Breathe.
Very good.
That's it. Now, just keep
your head nice and clear.
What are you doing?
- Jane's teaching Vega balance.
- Oh, that's useful.
- How long?
- Forty-three seconds.
Don't think.
If you have to think
thinking about dropping
will lead to dropping.
- What should I think about?
- Anything. S'mores.
I love s'mores.
Graham crackers
chocolate, marshmallows...
- Sixty seconds.
- Toasted on a campfire.
S'mores are better in a microwave.
It's true.
Well, I don't even know
what to say to that.
- Very good.
- Thank you.
- Is Agent Teresa Lisbon here?
- Hey, I'm Lisbon.
Julie Sandoval, US Attorney
for the Northern District.
What can I do for you?
I was upstairs getting a deposition
and I heard your name mentioned.
- Your brother is James Lisbon?
- What about him?
Have you spoken to him
in the last few days?
No. What's going on?
A warrant is being issued
for his arrest.
I thought you'd like to know.
What did he do?
He's a material witness
in a federal investigation.
A man named Nathan Barnes
was beaten to death ten days ago.
He's the son
of Judge Jacqueline Barnes.
We think your brother may have
been in contact with the victim
the night of the murder.
So they were in contact.
Arresting him
seems a little over-the-top.
- We'd prefer not to, but he fled.
- He what?
We sent officers to your brother's house
in Oklahoma City.
He slipped out the back door.
He hasn't responded to our attempts
to communicate with him.
- Can you reach him?
- Yeah. I think so.
Are you not close?
No, yeah, of cour... of course I can.
Tell him to turn himself in.
It'll be better that way.
Thanks for your time.
Yes, it's serious.
An arrest warrant is serious, Stan.
No, it's not okay.
What'd he say
when he called you?
Well, if you hear from him again
tell him to call me right away.
Stan says Jimmy called him
said he was in Chicago
but Stan doesn't know where he is.
Well, if he's in trouble
he's gonna go someplace
where he feels safe.
You know where that might be?
My parents' old house, probably.
Sounds right.
Hey.
Vega and Wylie filled me in.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
How many siblings do you have?
Three brothers.
I'm the oldest.
I'm the oldest of five.
Some days, keeping them in line...
You wanna strangle 'em.
All of them.
At the same time.
I'll clear your leave.
Take as much time
as you need.
Are you sure?
Go and take care
of your family.
I have to go to Chicago
find Jimmy, bring him back here.
Okay.
I should only be gone
a couple of days.
You know, I can come with you
if you want me to.
- That wouldn't be any fun for you.
- Fun's overrated.
If you wanna come
you can come.
Do you want me to?
I would very much like it
if you came.
All right.
Then I'm gonna come.
We'll do it together.
My parents bought
this house when I was three.
I lived here
all through high school.
I haven't been here
since my dad died.
This has got to stir up
some feelings for you.
Could use a lick of paint
but it's nice enough.
You don't have to be polite.
I never lived in a house
when I was a kid, Lisbon.
Little envy here.
It's still there.
Stan said he was fixing the place up
so his family could move in.
He didn't say it was a disaster.
Beer and pizza...
Jimmy was here.
I'm gonna go call Stan.
Okay.
Hey, where's your old bedroom?
"It's up the stairs.
First door on your right."
I love your, uh...
your wall graffiti there.
Jane?
- No.
- Jane?
- "What's going on?"
- No.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
- I take it that wasn't your brother.
- No.
Yeah. Yeah. Definitely. The drywall
will be in by the 12th.
- Hey, Stan.
- Hey, Teresa. Come in. Come in.
Let me finish up
with this butthole.
I'll be right with ya.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Where are your cowboy boots?
I expected cowboy boots
on the Chicago gal living in Texas.
Patrick, this is my sister-in-law, Karen.
- Hi.
- Is that Joey? Hi.
Joey's three and a half.
Him and Annie are at preschool.
This is Brian.
And you have a newborn
as well, right?
Paul. He's upstairs, asleep. Thank God.
- So, you're Patrick.
- Yeah.
It's fun to meet
one of Teresa's boyfriends.
She ever tell you
about Woody Squire?
- No.
- Have you heard from our brother?
The one who's in trouble
with the federal government?
Do you remember him?
Yeah, she doesn't wanna
talk about Woody Squire.
So, uh, Jimmy has, uh some information
about a... a murder or something?
Yeah, a guy named Nathan Barnes.
He's the son of a judge.
Well, Jimmy will be okay. I mean,
he's dumb but he's not stupid.
An arrest warrant is serious, Stan.
Oh, damn, I thought that nap
was gonna take.
Come on.
Let's go talk in the living room.
So, Woody Squire...
eyeliner and a lip ring.
He pierced himself...
got infected right before prom.
Swole up like a tennis ball.
- Ask her.
- Hilarious, Stan.
Uh, Jimmy called three days ago.
He said that I might hear from
some people that he was in town
but if anyone asked, I should
say I don't know where he is.
And you didn't think
that was suspicious?
I figured whatever Jimmy
got into, he could handle it.
Not all of us are cops, T.
And was anybody with him?
We went to Mom and Dad's house
to look for him
and somebody jumped Jane.
- Holy crap. You okay?
- Oh, yeah.
Right as rain. Thanks.
Wait, so this... this person
was, like, in the house.
You have any idea who it was?
No. I... I mean...
It must've been
somebody looking for Jimmy.
Uh, you know
he's playing cards again?
Great. Great.
So you think it's a poker thing?
Somebody's after Jimmy
to collect a gambling debt?
Definite possibility.
So, how's, uh...
how's business, Stan?
You're a... you're a contractor?
Yeah. Well, home-remodeling contractor.
- You know, kitchens, bathrooms.
- Nice. How's that going for you?
Things have been great.
Yeah, money's awesome.
Yeah.
I guess that explains why you haven't been
out to your parents' place.
That's a nice, little place.
Needs a little TLC, though.
Yeah, I've been swamped.
- Can we get back to Jimmy?
- Oh, absolutely, boss.
Uh, so what can I do?
Call his friends. See if any
of them have heard from him.
We're gonna check out the bars
in Bridgeport.
Sure.
Oh, I forgot. Uh, baby's
christening's on Saturday.
- Any chance you can make it?
- I'll try.
- Got it.
- What?
T, we all know with you
"I'll try," means, "I won't".
Look, I'd like to come.
It's just I got a job.
I got a job, too.
You're not the only busy person
on the planet.
It's fine. Hey...
Let me know if you can make it
all right?
I will. Yeah.
- Patrick, nice meeting you.
- You, too.
All right.
I'm sorry.
My family is messy.
Oh, no need.
- Messy people are good people.
- I'm not messy.
You're messy on the inside.
Wylie, what's up?
Hey, I talked to a friend
of mine in the Dallas office
got some info
on the Nathan Barnes murder.
What'd you find out?
They found his body in an alley
behind the Wrightwood Hotel
in Dallas ten days ago.
He'd been beaten to death.
The ME found bruising
and cracked ribs
in addition to a busted skull.
That doesn't sound like
a robbery gone wrong.
"Well, he did a lot of pro-bono
work for battered women."
Dallas cops think it was probably
an angry boyfriend or husband.
Well, why do they want
to talk to Jimmy about it?
Well, apparently, they found his
business card in Barnes' pocket.
That's weird.
All right, thanks.
Ah ah, don't hang up.
Thank you.
Wylie, it's Jane.
Yeah, I got in a little tussle with someone
when we first got here.
"Could you run a description
see what comes up?"
Yeah, sure.
Uh, hit me.
Male, Caucasian, hazel eyes,
brown hair, mustache, beard
"about 25 or 26 years old
6'4", 210 pounds"
an inch-long scar running
vertically under the left eye
and a tattoo of a spider
on the inner-right wrist.
That is pretty detailed.
Anything else?
Yeah. He smelled of Aqua Velva.
Aqua Velva.
I don't think there's anything uncommon
about that around here, though.
He's not here.
Teresa?
Teresa Lisbon?
T.J. Mullins.
- Hey, T.J.
- Hey, how's it going?
Oh, my God.
T.J. Mullins.
- I heard.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
This one used to babysit me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Remember when you sat for me
and I locked you out of the house
and you threw a brick
through the basement window to get back in?
And it was completely my fault
and you paid my dad
for the window.
You were such a straight arrow, Teresa.
Thanks. Uh, you know
we're looking for Jimmy.
- Have you seen him?
- No, I haven't seen him.
- Have you talked to him?
- No, no. Definitely not.
T.J., you seem like a very nice kid
but you're a terrible liar.
I'd bet we will find a call
from Jimmy on here.
Hey, where'd you get that?
- That's my phone.
- Yes, it is.
He called this morning.
Look, we need to find him.
It's important.
I said I wouldn't tell
if anybody came looking.
Uh, it's a family emergency.
Yeah.
He said something
about going fishing.
- That's all I got.
- Thanks.
Your mom called.
Should probably call her back.
See you, TJ.
Hey.
Sis, what are you
doing here?
There's a warrant out
for your arrest.
You're wanted for questioning
by the U.S. attorney
and you ran away.
Like do you have any idea
how much trouble you're in?
Catch anything?
No. Your boyfriend?
- Yeah. Patrick.
- Hi.
I wanna help.
- Did I ask for your help?
- No, but you're my brother.
Yeah, I'm your brother.
You know, it's funny
how I'm only your brother
when you think I messed up.
Look, talking to an FBI agent
is not a great idea
for me right now.
Talking to the feds is
gonna get me in hot water
with a very dangerous guy.
Who? The guy who came
looking for you at the house?
Someone was at the house?
Yeah, somebody
broke into the house.
Stan says he thinks he was there
to collect a gambling debt.
Or maybe it has something to do
with what happened in Dallas.
- What is it?
- You talked to Stan?
Yeah. Earlier today.
Is he right?
Was the guy
collecting a debt?
I don't know. Maybe.
You're gambling again?
Are you playing poker?
Would you back off me
for like one minute?
Uh, do you mind if I have a little talk
with your brother alone?
No offense, but "sister's boyfriend"
isn't exactly a position of authority to me.
Let me offer you a deal.
You come back to Texas
with your sister and me
and you'll never
have to testify.
And no one will ever know
that you helped us.
How do you swing that?
We'll catch the killer in a way that
your testimony will be unnecessary.
Just like that?
Well, I skipped a few steps
in the middle, but yeah.
I don't even know you, man.
Why should I trust you?
Because I haven't told your sister
about the man in the house
and why he was really there.
I know he's not from Dallas
and I don't think that he was there
to collect on a gambling debt.
Do I have to go on?
No.
Look, I... I don't like
keeping secrets from Teresa.
I care about her.
And I care about the people
that she cares about.
You come back to Texas
and you'll be fine. I promise.
We're good.
- This is where you work?
- It is, yeah.
Fancy.
Step up from the fryer
at Casper's.
It's probably better
for your face, too.
Hi. I'm Jimmy Lisbon.
- Can I help you?
- Jimmy, come on. Let's go.
Later.
- Get in.
- Okay.
You're recording me? You
gonna read me my rights first?
I have to put this on record.
It's for your own good.
What were you doing in Dallas
the night Nathan Barnes
was killed?
- You're gonna be mad.
- Jimmy.
Okay, but I don't wanna
hear about it.
I was at a poker game
at the Wrightwood Hotel.
You drove to Dallas
for a poker game?
It's three hours
from Oklahoma City.
You'd drive three hours
for a good game.
No, I wouldn't.
It must've been my other big sister
who taught me how to play cards.
Was the victim at the game?
Yeah. Nathan was there.
We got to talking.
He said he had some
electrical work needed done.
I gave him my card
said I was an electrician.
- Did you see him get killed?
- No way.
- Do you know who did it?
- No.
- Jimmy.
- T, look...
What happens is
I... I go to the Wrightwood, okay?
"And Nathan is there."
"I know him and a friend of his
named Charlie McInnis."
"He's another law clerk."
"They're the only ones I know...
by name, at least."
Do you remember anybody else
who was there?
A woman named Vicki, I think.
Met a dude named Ben.
You said there was somebody
there that you were afraid of.
Don't tell me
you can't remember his name.
The game's run by a guy
named George Holiday.
George Holiday, 50 years old.
He's a major player
in the Dallas organized-crime world.
Union kickbacks, sex trade, drugs
suspected of a few hits
in the '90s
before he moved
into management.
Mobster in cowboy boots
and a big-time gambler.
Nathan Barnes was in a ton of debt
to Holiday.
- How much?
- $140,000, $150,000.
He was a chatty drunk
after a few gin and tonics.
So, there you go.
Have fun catching him.
- I'm not sure Holiday's our guy.
- Why not?
It's hard to get money
out of a dead man.
The killer is almost certainly
a part of that poker game.
We need to get in on that.
Forget it.
Took me weeks.
I had to charm Holiday
with my mad poker skills.
Let us take care of it.
How do we find him?
He's a silent partner at an upscale sports
bar in Dallas called Donovan's.
I just had a contentious phone call
with US Attorney Sandoval.
Her office was alerted by TSA
about your brother's flight.
- She asked that we hand him over.
- Whoa.
I mean, you said that
I wouldn't have to do this.
Well, you won't... just yet.
I told her that
we caught a break in the case.
She wasn't happy, but she agreed
to let us follow it for 72 hours.
Now, if we find a suspect in
that time, the collar is hers.
If we don't, then we need
to rethink our strategy.
Uh, Cho and I need
to make friends with a mobster.
We're gonna need some cash.
I'll see what I can do.
Jane, that guy who attacked you
in Chicago?
Mm-hmm?
I found someone who fit
the description you gave.
Name's Delfino.
Low-level thug. It's odd, though.
Lisbon said he was after Jimmy
but I can't find any connection
between the two.
Delfino's Chicago, born-and-bred.
No connection
to Oklahoma city or Dallas.
If he was after Jimmy
I don't know
who he was working for.
Want the locals to pick him up?
No. Uh, let's sit on this
and don't tell anyone, okay?
Sure thing.
Holiday.
- They're gonna run it.
- They're gonna pass.
Okay, let's put it up there.
Let's see, shall we?
Come on, now.
- Here we are. $60.
- You're on.
Run it. Run it.
- Yes.
- Oh.
- I do love taking your money.
- Well, I'll have my revenge.
Mm-hmm.
- Another?
- Yeah.
Uh, bartender, two more drinks.
Oh, drinks on me.
Sir, you want a drink?
I'm buying.
- I buy my own drinks, thanks.
- Smart man.
Never put yourself
in another person's debt.
Uh, let's make this a little
more interesting, shall we?
A thousand says next drive
ties the game.
- That's too much for me.
- Nah. $1,000. Come on.
$1,000.
Anyone want in?
Money on the bar.
Do you know anything
about football?
Why don't you take the bet
and find out?
You ought to be more careful
with your money...
and your mouth.
Thank you...
For the advice.
Goodness, you look delicious.
Eh, fishing with the wrong bait.
Charlie McInnis?
I'm Agent Michelle Vega.
I'd like to talk to you about the murder
of judge Barnes' son, Nathan.
Sure.
Yeah, terrible what happened.
Um, Heidi Pendleton.
This is my fiancée.
We work with Judge Barnes.
Hi.
Nathan was an amazing guy.
- I... um, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Uh... It seems so senseless
what happened.
I helped Nathan with some
of his domestic-abuse cases.
We became friends through that.
Nathan was at a poker game
the night he got killed.
You were there, too
weren't you, Mr. McInnis?
Yes.
- So you know George Holiday.
- Yeah, but just from the game.
Who else did you know
at the game?
Um... Nathan, obviously
a kid named
Jimmy Lisbon
uh, there was a woman
named Vicki Shell
and Benjamin Bennett.
- You played poker with Bennett?
- Yeah, it was nothing.
What do you know
about Benjamin Bennett?
Judge Barnes ruled against him
in a patent case a few months back.
He was ticked off.
There was a lot of money involved.
That's how we know him.
You know, through the paperwork.
And the poker game?
Isn't that a conflict of interest?
I mean, I never discussed
the case with him.
But someone did?
Well, Bennett was working Nathan
about it
wanted to get his mom
to revisit the ruling.
Nathan said no, of course
but, uh, Bennett wouldn't let it go.
So, there were six players
at the poker game.
George Holiday.
Nathan was in debt to Holiday
for 140 grand.
That's a big chip
for Holiday to play.
Charlie McInnis?
"He lost big that night.
Not a good night for him."
"Benjamin Bennett
goes by Benben."
Former college basketball star
trying to make it as an entrepreneur.
The victim's mother ruled
against him in a patent case.
"Vicki Shell, avid cyclist and CEO
of a Dallas bicycle manufacturer."
"According to Jimmy
she had an eye for the victim."
You're sure one of them
killed Nathan?
Well, it seems likely.
We won't know for sure
until we get into the game.
Well, how'd it go with Holiday?
You in?
Not yet.
He needs a different kind
of motivation.
What kind?
Scotch on the rocks, please.
- On the house.
- Thank you, kind stranger.
- George, please.
- Teresa.
Teresa.
So, what's your story, Teresa?
I gotta tell you something, buddy.
You got a much better sense
about women
than you do about football.
Well, it's just money.
You really mean that
you've never been broke.
Well, what's the point
of having money
if you can't have fun with it, right?
Betting on sports is fun
but, uh, there's no skill in it.
Gets boring after a while.
You play cards?
He's terrible at poker.
- Stop it. You're drunk.
- You're drunk.
I'm good at cards.
He lost $27,000
in one poker game
and then he told me
it was fun.
It was fun.
It was fun... for a while.
I mean here's the thing with cards.
It's like a showdown
in the Wild West... kill or be killed.
I mean, who doesn't love that?
It's nothing like that at all.
You know, I might
know of a game... big one.
Five grand buy-in. Is that
something that might interest you?
Deal me in there, partner.
Jane's in the game.
- The Wrightwood Hotel?
- Presidential suite.
We're gonna need surveillance
cameras all over that place.
You got a plan
for getting them in?
Yeah, I believe we do.
The wedding's next year
and we were thinking
about holding it here at the Wrightwood.
And then we were shopping
and thought, "What they hey?"
"Let's check it out."
- It's nice, huh?
- I guess.
Well, we actually have an array
of all-inclusive wedding packages.
We just wanna see the room.
Oh. Of course.
This here.
And here we go.
And the table is set up
for an event tonight.
Wow.
This is really nice.
I think this could work, honey.
You think. Hmm?
Do you care what I think?
- You don't like it.
- Does it matter?
You only care
about what your mother likes.
Don't talk about my mother.
Oh, I think we need
to talk about your mother.
No, I think you need
to calm down.
Do not tell me to calm down.
Seriously, you're embarrassing me.
I'll leave you to talk things over.
I'll be at the front desk
if you need me.
Camera in the corner
camera on the counter
camera on the thermostat.
I didn't know you were
gonna flip to Spanish.
Kind of a spur-of-the-moment thing.
Did you understand?
Something about
ripping my head off?
You've been studying.
Hand me the wrench.
Thanks.
You don't see it at all.
How's the toilet?
Busted.
Excellent. Let's go.
Hello?
Teresa, I didn't know who else to call.
- Karen? What's wrong?
- Stan got beat up.
Oh, my God.
Is he okay?
He said it was an accident at work.
I don't believe him.
"Leave it alone, T."
No. Your wife
is scared to death.
- Who did this?
- "A couple of guys got drunk"
"and were looking
for trouble, all right?"
That's not what you told Karen.
Uh, why are you lying to me?
"I'm not."
Look, I know crap
when I hear it, Stan.
I am gonna kill Jimmy
for getting you involved in this.
"Just stay out of it.
Please?"
I'll talk to you later.
Gotta catch that.
What's going on with Stan?
What? Nothing.
That's what Jane was talking
to you about at the lake.
Why you agreed
to come out here.
You're hiding something
about Stan.
Jimmy... come on.
Tell me what's going on.
Stan had a couple bad breaks
in his business.
Karen's last pregnancy
was tough.
He got behind on his bills.
He owes money
to the wrong people.
A loan shark.
What's he in for?
Over 30 grand.
Thirty? God.
The man that attacked Jane...
he wasn't looking for you.
He was there for Stan.
Why'd you cover for him?
Stan, he's... he's working
so hard to be good.
Just wanted you to be proud of him.
I am proud of him.
I'm proud of all of you.
Really?
Did you call me when
I got my electrician's license?
You only call to yell at me
just like always.
Look, I know I was tough on you
when you were a kid, but come on.
You know what mom and dad were like.
Somebody had to be responsible
and somebody had to be in charge.
Yeah?
You were in charge.
Then you left.
- So, Jimmy's gonna be part of this?
- Yeah. Has to be.
- He's gonna play in the game?
- I need him there.
Well, then I'm gonna be there.
He'll be safe.
We'll have eyes on them.
He's my little brother.
I'm gonna be there.
Yeah, of course.
How's it gonna go?
Jimmy's gonna make contact
with all the suspects.
"Holiday's sending the invitation."
"Jimmy's gonna make sure
they show up."
- McInnis.
- Charlie, hey.
It's Jimmy from the poker game.
Well, hello, Jimmy from the poker game.
What's going on?
Did you get
George Holiday's invitation?
"There's a game tonight."
"And then he will use the word"
"that makes every poker player
smell blood."
I'm telling you, Ben.
This guy's a whale. Okay?
One of my friends played with him.
This guy dropped like $20,000
in one night.
For real?
He's a terrible player.
Doesn't care
if he wins or loses.
Just wants action.
We'll clean him out.
Where are we with the surveillance?
Cameras coming online...
Now.
Holiday, Jimmy Lisbon
Charlie McInnis, Vicki Shell
and Benben are in the room.
All right. Tell Jane
and Lisbon we're ready.
Yep.
That was Wylie.
They're all set.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Um, yeah, I'm ready.
Let's go.
Your brothers don't hate you, you know.
- Yeah, they do.
- No, they don't.
Jimmy's right.
I left.
After my mom died
I was the parent, and I left.
Well, you felt trapped.
Of course you did.
Now Stan's life is a mess
Jimmy's got a gambling problem
and God only knows
what Tommy's up to.
Yeah, sure, look
they've got their problems.
But they're good people.
And they wouldn't even be here
if you hadn't loved and protected them
when they were kids.
You're uncomfortable around them
because you feel guilt.
I understand that.
But you need to know
they're not mad at you.
They're not.
They just miss you.
You knew exactly
what was going on
with Stan and Jimmy
and the guy at the house.
You figured it out
and you didn't say a word to me.
Well...
It's not my business.
Thank you.
All right, let's go.
- We've got a game to get to.
- Absolutely.
- Welcome.
- You remember Teresa?
I'm just here to watch.
Make yourself at home, darling.
Take any more of my money
you're gonna have to buy me dinner.
We'll see.
"That was a bad beat
last week, Charlie."
You don't have to do anything
other than play poker.
Focus on the game.
Let me do the work.
- What work, exactly?
- You'll see.
First, another drink.
Toilet's busted.
- Plugged?
- It's not flushing.
Don't go in there.
All right, so what do you guys wanna do?
You wanna pull up stakes
and take it to another room?
We... we're gonna relocate
just because there's a plumbing snafu?
I mean, I... I... I didn't come here
to go to the bathroom.
I came here to play poker.
Let's just play poker.
Man wants to play cards.
- So be it.
- Okay with me
All right.
There is a washroom down
at the end of the hall by the health club.
- All right.
- Take a walk or hold your water.
Patrick Jane.
That's my girlfriend, Teresa.
I'm just here to watch
and enjoy the open bar.
The game is Texas Hold'em.
No limit.
Start off a little slow.
And away we go.
"All right, ante up.
Gotta be on the decline."
- "Yeah."
- So, is Jane cheating?
Yeah, but he isn't playing to win.
He's watching the other players
so he can learn their tells.
Oh, what do we have
on Fourth Street, here?
Subtle behaviors a player makes
when he has a good
or a bad hand.
I know what a tell is.
Nose rub.
Last time she did that
she got a flush.
The nose rub is her tell.
Ha. Told you.
Okay, game on.
Rocking.
He rocks side to side.
Oh! Eyebrow scratch.
Hair scratch.
That's all of them.
Time for phase two.
So, it's back to me, huh?
Well, we all feeling good?
Are we feeling all right there, honey?
I don't know.
There's something disturbing
in this room.
Ah, she's a little sensitive
a little psychic.
- Psychic?
- Almost.
Was somebody
killed here recently?
Oh, my God.
Uh, not in this room, but, yeah
one of our players was killed.
Nate... no.
Uh, Nathan.
- Is... is that his name?
- This is getting a little weird.
Amazing, isn't she?
Uh, it's kind of uncanny.
Yeah.
We're playing poker, aren't we?
- I'm in.
- I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait.
- Uh, Th... there's more.
- There is?
I'm feeling a darker presence.
The killer is in this room.
- Oh, come on.
- One of you killed Nathan.
Wait.
Don't touch your cards.
The killer is the one who has the ace.
I think things just got interesting.
She says the killer's
holding an ace.
I'm curious.
It's McInnis.
Looks like daddy's
going to the big house.
Whoops.
Gonna go get myself a drink.
Not so much of a psychic
after all, I guess.
Now, can we play some cards?
So, are we ready to go?
Not yet.
Now Jane makes sure
McInnis wins.
- Ah, take it.
- Oh, look out, daddy.
Lucky guy.
- You're good. You're good.
- Boy, you're hot.
- You're having a good night.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, I am now
gonna take the long walk
to the little boy's room.
I'm feeling a little warm.
I don't know about anyone else.
Time for a drink.
Or two.
Can I get you something?
What the hell is this?
- What?
- Honey, we're leaving.
- What? Why?
- We're in the middle of a game.
Uh, there's a hidden camera here.
- Are you kidding?
- What?
There.
Camera?
What the hell?
Mr. McInnis.
Agent Kimball Cho, FBI.
- What is this? What's going on?
- We know you killed Nathan Barnes.
What?
That's ridiculous.
Our agents in the room
are telling Holiday it was you.
McInnis has been winning
all night.
He's got someone watching in
another room, feeding him cards.
Oh, geez.
Now, Barnes owed Holiday
a lot of money.
By killing Nathan Barnes
you cheated him out of it.
This is a live feed.
Turn yourself in for the murder
and we'll protect you.
Look, I don't know what this is
but this is really crazy.
Have fun telling Holiday that.
McInnis, come on back.
We're waiting on you.
Come on, son.
It's your turn to deal.
Come on back and play.
Get me out of here.
Good choice.
Let's go.
Where you going?
My fiancée, Heidi
started spending a lot of time
helping Nathan
with his pro-bono legal work.
I suspected she was cheating on me.
I didn't have proof
until Nathan showed up
at the game that night.
"I was losing that night... bad."
"Something was off."
"Then I figured it out."
Nathan was wearing
one of my shirts.
How'd you know
it was your shirt?
My monogram on the cuff.
Nathan was sleeping with Heidi.
Must've grabbed one of my shirts
at her apartment instead of his.
He took a lot of money
from me that night
and he... he smirked
when he did it.
Ugh, that little bastard. He
was just rubbing it in my face.
He knew I knew
and he loved it.
"I followed him out."
"I confronted him."
He had the nerve to deny it...
deny all of it.
"But he was wearing the proof."
We spoke with your fiancée.
Heidi had gone to coffee
with Nathan in her neighborhood that day.
Nathan spilled coffee
on his shirt
and she gave him one
of your clean shirts to borrow.
The only thing he ever did
to you was beat you in cards.
- Nice party.
- This is how we do it.
Hey.
- Cheers.
- Hey, where's my beer?
Oh, Texas girls drink margaritas.
- Give me the beer.
- Okay.
Hey, we got, uh, burgers
brats, veggie-patty crap
if you want veggie-patty crap.
- Your face looks better.
- Eh, it's still a little sore.
I know you're in trouble, Stan.
Whatever I can do to help
let me help.
You don't have to do that.
I know I don't have to.
I want to.
Just enough to keep you
from getting punched in the face again.
I kind of thought you wouldn't mind
seeing me get punched in the face.
I'm the only one who gets to punch you.
- Okay. I'm good.
- You want one?
Hey, I'm glad
you made it out.
It means a lot.
And Karen's family
was really impressed with you.
I'm impressed with you.
I'm proud of you, T.
Thanks.
- We should hang out more.
- Oh, like normal people?
Yeah, like normal people.
We should.
This has been fun.
It's too bad Woody Squire
couldn't make it.
- It's a real shame about that.
- Yeah.
Shut up.
"What's that behind your ear?"
We talked about Patrick.
- You did, did you?
- Yeah.
We like him.
He's a good guy.
Don't mess this one up, okay?
I'll try not to.
I'm glad we came back home.
Me too.
It was nice.
I don't think I've said this.
I mean, I know I haven't said this
but I don't really know
if I need to
because you always know
what I'm thinking.
Well, not everything.
Would you be surprised
if I said I love you?
I'd be...
I'd be lying if I didn't say
I would be moved by that.
I love you.
I said it.
I'm surprised.